Guide to the Stuart Elliott papers, 1875-2014 and undated RL.11108
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Large-Format Materials, 1931-2014 and undated; 8
  - Advertisement--St. Louis Post-Dispatch baseball posters, 1998 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--The Healing Garden, 2008 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Thomas Pink, undated (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Time Walter Mondale, 1984 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Toys R Us Christmas, 2014 (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Truth vs. Advertising, undated (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Wrigley Doublemint, undated (Box OV2)
  - Advertisement--Volkswagen, Vogue, Calvin Klein, Abercrombie Fitch, 1995-1999 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Advertising agencies--BBDO 1891 (100th anniversary), 1991 (Box OV3)
  - Advertising agencies--J. Walter Thompson "Advertising Leadership 1864-1989) (Box OV3)
  - Advertising agencies--Ogilvy Red magazine, 2007 (Box OV3)
  - Movies and television--Fast Lane poster, undated (Box OV3)
  - Movies and television--Private Parts, 1997 (Box OV3)
  - Movies and television--Star Wars Episode 1 promotions, 1999 (Box OV3)
  - Movies and television--The Legend of Tarzan, 1999 (Box OV3)
  - Movies and television--Homeland, 2011 (Box OV3)
  - Movies and television--Justified, 2011 (Box OV3)
  - Movies and television--Nickelodeon, 2014 (Box OV3)
  - Movies and television--Seinfeld final episode media kit, 1998 (Box OV3)
  - Photographs, 1988 (Box OV4)
  - Print material--Advertising Age, 1980, 2005-2013; 8 folders (Box OV4)
  - Print material--Automotive News (Chevrolet 100th anniversary), 2011 (Box OV4)
  - Print material--The Advertising Century, 1999 (Box OV4)
  - Print material--The House that Ivory Built (Procter Gamble 150th anniversary), 1987 (Box OV4)
  - Print material--Adweek, Stuart Elliott 10th anniversary as New York Times columnist, 2001 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Brand Underground (Rob Walker, New York Times Magazine), 2006 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Campaign (UK) silver jubilee 1968-1993 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Campaign (UK) World's leading agencies, 2002-2007 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Detroit Free Press, 1980 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Footwear News, 2002 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Hearst, Thirty Days of Fashion, undated (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Liberty Magazine covers (feature in Esquire), undated (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Life Magazine, McDonald's 35th anniversary, 1990 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Life Magazine return issue, 2004 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Meredith Publishing, Evening of Inspiration, 2007 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--New Stanley Hotel (Peter Vanderwicken, Esquire), undated (Box OV5)
  - Print material--NYC2012 Olympics plan/proposal, 2001 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--PRWeek Cause Roundtable feature, 2007 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Robert Coen (McCann-Erickson) reports on ad spending, 1991-2000 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--Sports Illustsrated 25th anniversary, 1979 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--The Glass Closet (Eve Kahn, Print magazine, LGBT content), 1994 (Box OV5)
  - Print material--The Onion 1783 parody, undated (Box OV5)
- Audiovisual Materials, 2001-2012 and undated; 9
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original audiovisual materials are closed to researchers until use copies can be produced. Consult Research Services staff for more information.
  - 20/20 fine print story, Corelle, Chrysler, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-001)
  - Middle Collegiate Church. Evolution is a Christian Concept--Multicultural Future. The Power of Story: Living into God's Reign leadership conference, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-002)
  - The Beauty Show sponsor presentation, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-003)
  - Twenty Four (television series) press kid, 2001 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-004)
  - Fragrance Foundation Seeing Scents 1950-2005 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-005)
  - Pepsico Media Services: Bob Newhart, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-006)
  - J.M. Melton Design Group, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-007)
  - CNBC Titans: Leo Burnett, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-008)
  - What Happened? Successful Strategies, Marketing Misdeeds, and the Brands that Loved Them, 2010 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-009)
  - Aaron Krach indestructible Artifact #12 (17 versions of "I will always love you"), 2009 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-010)
  - SLIQ 2(x)ist press kit, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-011)
  - MTVU Engine Room Highlights: Challenge 1 Latin America; Challenge 2 Europe, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-012)
  - Kaplan Thaler Group agency reel, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-013)
  - Ad Council/GLSEN files, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-014)
  - Honda Dream the Impossible documentary series: Mobility 2088, Failure, Kick Out the Ladder, 2009 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-015)
  - Trust Me pilot and episode 1, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-016)
  - Trust Me pilot and episode 1, 2008 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11108-DVD-017)
  - Trust Me press kit, 2008 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11108-DVD-018)
  - NBCUniversal: Y Now television or computer version, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-019)
  - NBCUniversal: Y Now computer version, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-020)
  - New York Life Insurance Company 2008 ad campaign. TRT 1:40 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-021)
  - Barfly: In the Bars with Barfly; Anheuser-Busch Demo., 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-022)
  - The Healing Garden 2008 advertising (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-023)
  - Fox Super Bowl promos, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-024)
  - Tower Laboratories Bromo Seltzer: Bromo Burp, Overindulgence., 2006 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-025)
  - Blairex Laboratories Simply Saline: Sasha :15, 2006 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-026)
  - Alka-Seltzer "Try It" original BBDO, undated (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-027)
  - Alka-Seltzer "Try It You'll Like It" Ketchum remake, 2006 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-028)
  - Music from The Prize Winner of Defiance Ohio. TRT: 58:07, 2005 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-029)
  - Jingle music from The Prize Winner of Defiance Ohio., 2005 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-030)
  - The Philanthropist press screener, 2009 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-031)
  - Not a Cough in a Carload tobacco ads, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-032)
  - Aflac "Whoodunit?", 2009 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-033)
  - Pepsi "Bob's House" final, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-034)
  - Drive and Deliver rough cut, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-035)
  - Concept Farm vs. Tour de France elements, 2008 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-036)
  - AMC The Pitch 101 promo reel; TRT 4:30, 2012 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-037)
  - The Pitch Waste Management Episode 102 picture lock, 2012 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-038)
  - The Pitch Subway Episode 101 Network rough cut 2, 2012 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-039)
  - Be Real: Stories from Queer America, 2007 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-040)
  - Showdown MvA Superbowl trailer, 1:30, 2009 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-041)
  - Euro-RSCG BETC Home, 2010 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-042)
  - Animal Planet Puppy Bowl IX sneak peak, 2013 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-043)
  - Got Milk? White Gold $50K High School Contest Top 15 Entries, 2010 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-044)
  - VisitHouston.com: H-town presents (compilation of 19 songs), 2011 (Box AV1, Dvd RL11108-DVD-045)
  - REO Speedwagon casual game/Windows; Curious Sense, 2009 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11108-DVD-046)
  - Henry firearms; RFD-TV live show, 2008 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11108-DVD-047)
  - WNET: The Real Mad Men and Women of Madison Avenue screening copy., 2013 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11108-DVD-048)
  - USA: Necessary Roughness; "Regret Me Not"; "There's the Door", 2013 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11108-DVD-049)
  - Absolut Vodka, 2011 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11108-DVD-050)
  - CW Network: CW 09 Brand Sizzles, 2009 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11108-DVD-051)
  - Glee/Fashion Night Out: Laird+Partners. TRT: 7:15, 2011 (Box AV2, Dvd RL11108-DVD-052)
  - That 80's Show, 2002 (Box AV2, Audio-phonodisc RL11108-LP-001)